[
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7a7dece7-eb61-4cfc-917c-6043cc9cfebf",
        "correctAnswer": "You need technology, you need the professions, but you also need something that speaks to the heart.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Technology decreases your ability to recognize beauty.",
            "The purpose of education is to build professional opportunities.",
            "Studying great art helps you see the interconnectedness of all areas of knowledge."
        ],
        "question": "1-President Gordon B. Hinckley said that a study of the humanities \u201cgives an aspect of living that is essential.\u201d He believed:",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "de3e2bf9-16cf-4a6a-9f69-8b83a8290888",
        "correctAnswer": "The aulos",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The trumpet",
            "The lyre",
            "The flute"
        ],
        "question": "2-What instrument did worshippers of Dionysus play?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e3b55625-4c98-499e-875a-9e235a47c934",
        "correctAnswer": "Doric",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Romanesque",
            "Corinthian",
            "Ionic"
        ],
        "question": "4-What is the name of the simplest and earliest of the Greek orders?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "035cfbfa-6cea-4de6-adbf-e7d64413ac01",
        "correctAnswer": "ambulatory, triforium, clerestory",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "nave, crossing, choir",
            "north aisle, south aisle, north transept, south transept",
            "nave, transept, aspe"
        ],
        "question": "5-What are the levels of a Gothic cathedral from bottom to top?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "746078e1-1551-45e0-9159-9c95a68eebd0",
        "correctAnswer": "A barrel vault",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "An Oculus",
            "Keystone",
            "Triumphal arch"
        ],
        "question": "6-What do we call a vault created by a series of arches?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5abd3e72-6e3f-4dd6-b03b-de63896d7272",
        "correctAnswer": "Outside, in front of the entrance.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Between columns and a concrete wall.",
            "Under an arch",
            "At the foot of the god or goddess statue."
        ],
        "question": "7-Where was the altar placed in a Greek temple?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d3fbc809-8bb8-4fc9-8acd-9a7cc7fef2dc",
        "correctAnswer": "Romanesque",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Polyphony between form and function",
            "Maslow's hierarchy of needs",
            "Dionysian"
        ],
        "question": "8-What is the name of the style of the early Middle Ages that uses Roman arches, domes, and barrel vaults?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0b735a44-f675-4ea2-bf74-f8254c4ce0a1",
        "correctAnswer": "Hagia Sophia (was built in the sixth century AD in Constantinople)",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "St. Sernin Basilica",
            "Parthenon",
            "Colosseum"
        ],
        "question": "9-What is the name of the great domed church of Constantinople?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "16aa389e-c409-417c-869d-bb874aba0379",
        "correctAnswer": "Flying buttresses",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Lintel and post",
            "Barrel vault",
            "Romanesque"
        ],
        "question": "10-What were the structures used to brace the outside of a Gothic cathedral called?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d4004a69-60a0-4979-9175-14dda6fc00c9",
        "correctAnswer": "Scholasticism",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Christianity",
            "Life of the Mind",
            "Pagan"
        ],
        "question": "11-What do we call the philosophy that the world is rational and that we come to understand it through the Spirit?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8ffe5f8c-13f3-4e5b-8bff-3efd7e4daa95",
        "correctAnswer": "Christian services are meant to be indoors, to shelter them from the world whereas pagan architecture was open to both the sight of the gods they worshipped and the world.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Aesthetic principles",
            "Building materials",
            "Public life vs. family-oriented privacy"
        ],
        "question": "12-What accounts for the differences between pagan and Christian architecture?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "21027b94-9d49-44f4-ad20-050909000a82",
        "correctAnswer": "Ionic",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Corinthian",
            "Doric",
            "Romanesque"
        ],
        "question": "14-What Greek order uses a scroll shaped capital?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0dc4e49b-4346-4ac6-a6ad-0bc77c4421eb",
        "correctAnswer": "Horns",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Trombone",
            "Trumpet",
            "Tuba"
        ],
        "question": "15-Which brass instruments get their names because in ancient times they were made from a long, curled ram's horn?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "6bcf6207-1d32-4f02-b69b-dc63f1cd4c6e",
        "correctAnswer": "The soprano is always a woman",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The soprano is higher than the alto",
            "The tenor is usually a man",
            "The bass is lower than the tenor"
        ],
        "question": "17-Which statement is not true?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "396732e4-9a5e-4a81-86cc-dbd537938fcc",
        "correctAnswer": "Clarinet",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Trumpet",
            "Drums",
            "String Bass"
        ],
        "question": "18-What instrument did Benny Goodman play?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "13ddfa9d-2f18-40fb-9d72-d406cc25fe47",
        "correctAnswer": "Brass instruments have reeds",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The various string instruments relate to the ranges of the human voice",
            "Percussion instruments include the timpani and xylophone",
            "The harpsichord is a keyboard instrument"
        ],
        "question": "19-Which statement is not true?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e1fb654e-77c8-44d0-8922-be5be9207e5b",
        "correctAnswer": "Violin",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Cello",
            "Organ",
            "Trumpet"
        ],
        "question": "21-Which instrument plays the solo passages in Vivaldi's Four Seasons",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e3dd76a7-8b8c-4ac0-aaa3-9f598773d1d1",
        "correctAnswer": "A large ensemble is called a chamber ensemble",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Many choirs include sopranos, altos, tenors, and basses",
            "A band is a group of instruments that does not include bowed strings",
            "Strings are at the heart of an orchestra"
        ],
        "question": "22-Which statement is not true?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c3b62fe8-e387-4084-a6bd-b9943eb32394",
        "correctAnswer": "Because they were originally made of wood.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Because they must correspond to the ranges of the human voice.",
            "Because they are plucked or bowed.",
            "Because players hold them vertically."
        ],
        "question": "23-Why do woodwinds have a softer, mellower sound than brass instruments?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "218295eb-7eac-4189-89ad-ec31edeb0975",
        "correctAnswer": "The Paris Opera . (Palais Garnier)",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Rome Opera",
            "The Venice Opera",
            "The Metropolitan Opera"
        ],
        "question": "24-What is the setting for the Phantom of the Opera?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "11f4847c-9afc-472a-bfbb-d2b09197b7ba",
        "correctAnswer": "The trumpet is deeper than the horn",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The trombone is lower than the trumpet",
            "The clarinet is a woodwind instrument",
            "The trumpet is higher than the tuba"
        ],
        "question": "25-Which statement is not true?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d034523e-bc97-47ae-9c83-c663b1c687ac",
        "correctAnswer": "Any of these",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Glass",
            "Tile",
            "Stone"
        ],
        "question": "26-In mosaic, to make a picture an artist arranges pieces of",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "710704f8-a0f4-410b-a8a1-ced520606d3e",
        "correctAnswer": "1400s",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "1600s",
            "1200s",
            "1500s"
        ],
        "question": "27-When was oil-based painting pioneered?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "6e3dc262-cbfe-460a-964a-772607fc714e",
        "correctAnswer": "copper",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "silver",
            "lead",
            "gold"
        ],
        "question": "28-To make an engraving the artist takes a flat plate of soft metal and scratches the desired picture into the surface. Which soft metal is usually used:",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "6c2729b4-9dd5-4f76-9b6d-d5026fd62727",
        "correctAnswer": "What it's made of.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Where it's made.",
            "How it's made.",
            "It's category or grouping."
        ],
        "question": "29-What is an artwork's medium?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7748c658-4311-427c-8160-b50b14ffcdac",
        "correctAnswer": "It lacks the fine precise detail of other forms.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The colored surface fades.",
            "The paint is immediately absorbed.",
            "The paint tends to flake off or become damaged."
        ],
        "question": "30-Identify a limitation of woodcut:",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "04f7c6fc-5cab-4d78-b2b0-a996a0c66e6e",
        "correctAnswer": "days or even weeks",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "several months",
            "a few hours",
            "a few minutes"
        ],
        "question": "31-How long does it take oil based paint to dry?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "99cf58a5-7702-47d9-b97e-ede1844451c2",
        "correctAnswer": "King Francis the First",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Louis-Philippe I",
            "Charles X",
            "Napoleon Bonaparte"
        ],
        "question": "32-Which French monarch purchased the Mona Lisa?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "db0e92a1-4e9c-4216-b616-e48df623a50d",
        "correctAnswer": "The colors are fast and permanent",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Last Supper is a mural",
            "All the statements are true",
            "It is painted on a wall"
        ],
        "question": "33-What is not true of a mural?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d0df3c6b-12b2-4da3-9674-584ea375f769",
        "correctAnswer": "The palace of the French kings",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "An orphanage",
            "A hospital",
            "A military barracks"
        ],
        "question": "34-What was the Louvre before it was a museum?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "39406130-45a4-447f-bd82-ab9f0b095e75",
        "correctAnswer": "Low",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Long",
            "Large",
            "Sharp"
        ],
        "question": "35-Bas in bas relief means",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7207fa03-94af-4039-a257-473ba3cc90a4",
        "correctAnswer": " 1504",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "1520",
            "1516",
            "1400"
        ],
        "question": "36-What year did Leonardo begin the Mona Lisa?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b7e60a3e-ca96-4e69-981c-6ed12c408953",
        "correctAnswer": "It allowed for ongoing revisions and blending of the colors.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "It allowed Leonardo to paint on a surface other than canvas.",
            "It. provided a transparent background which reflected through the paint layers.",
            "It protected the pigment from water washes."
        ],
        "question": "37-What did oil-based paint make possible in regards to the Mona Lisa?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ebed61f0-4645-479e-81a8-b78a7bcc61c9",
        "correctAnswer": "A fortress",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A palace",
            "An art museum",
            "Residence of the French Kings"
        ],
        "question": "38-What was the Louvre originally designed to be?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b53a07a6-379d-4c17-a6b3-d0c04e0f0503",
        "correctAnswer": "The Rule of Thirds",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Allegory of the Cave",
            "The Pythagorean Theorem",
            "The Birth of the Blues"
        ],
        "question": "39-What is a simplified version of the Golden Section?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b8c29f52-ec31-4b06-8575-afdd76e94210",
        "correctAnswer": "true",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "False",
            ".",
            ","
        ],
        "question": "40-Red and green are complimentary colors.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "39ed7379-ff8f-4f2b-8e4d-e4391aeb1d64",
        "correctAnswer": "Texture",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Perspective",
            "Foreshortening",
            "Value"
        ],
        "question": "41-The 19th century artist Vincent Van Gogh is famous for his dramatic brushstrokes and thick globs of paint. Which artistic element is this?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b922054f-a8f9-41c9-b65d-c23cfc1a0992",
        "correctAnswer": "Green",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Red",
            "Blue",
            "Yellow"
        ],
        "question": "42-Which is not a primary color?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c9ec3181-321d-4b3f-8609-a3bb04fa5fd9",
        "correctAnswer": "Repeating certain shapes, colors, etc.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Balance vertical patterns.",
            "Include lines running from left to right across the work.",
            "Include symmetrical and radial shapes."
        ],
        "question": "43-How do artists emphasize the emotional impact of a work?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "71325b80-650a-45c1-83ae-49b3353e2a71",
        "correctAnswer": "The contrast between light and darkness",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The formula for creating perspective",
            "None of the above",
            "The Rule of Thirds"
        ],
        "question": "44-Chiaroscuro refers to________.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5892fb71-7475-426f-9963-20fc3cfa0008",
        "correctAnswer": "An s-curve",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A slow curve",
            "A diagonal line",
            "A horizontal line"
        ],
        "question": "45-What type of line is considered most pleasing to the eye?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "07ce6223-9119-4c90-8c12-6b44c2545642",
        "correctAnswer": "Texture",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "None of the above",
            "Glaze",
            "Fresco"
        ],
        "question": "46-The visual appearance of the surface of the canvas is called_______.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8283092f-8cf1-4884-91ce-d755708a117d",
        "correctAnswer": "Repeating certain shapes, colors, etc.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Balance vertical patterns.",
            "Include lines running from left to right across the work.",
            "Include symmetrical and radial shapes."
        ],
        "question": "47-How do artists emphasize the emotional impact of a work?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "02631ccb-4a46-400e-8453-37467ae25bf8",
        "correctAnswer": "Red",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Black",
            "Yellow",
            "White"
        ],
        "question": "48-The 17th Century painter, Peter Paul Rubens, used a great deal of what color in \"The Stroke of the Lance\" to emphasize the violence of Christ's crucifixion?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ba0ed55f-92ae-4643-b8d5-ba3342413af5",
        "correctAnswer": "Texture",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Foreshortening",
            "Perspective",
            "Value"
        ],
        "question": "49-The 19th century artist Vincent Van Gogh is famous for his dramatic brushstrokes and thick globs of paint. Which artistic element is this?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3d69ef33-2a63-4f98-a501-8762acaf2eae",
        "correctAnswer": "The Rule of Thirds",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Birth of the Blues",
            "The Allegory of the Cave",
            "The Pythagorean Theorem"
        ],
        "question": "50-What is a simplified version of the Golden Section?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a31b8447-0496-4be1-b262-72df74c2aba8",
        "correctAnswer": "True",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "False",
            ",",
            "."
        ],
        "question": "51-A diagonal line indicates action.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "f3516c3c-4e28-4e02-9a51-93e9361864e5",
        "correctAnswer": "Foreshadowing.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Complication",
            "Irony",
            "Peripety."
        ],
        "question": "52-In the tragedy Oedipus Rex, Oedipus questions a blind man who refuses to tell him anything. Oedipus curses him for being so uncooperative; the blind man's reply is an example of what?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ad6cfc67-e2b8-4a99-a800-1e1840aea373",
        "correctAnswer": "Sophocles",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Aristotle",
            "Arles",
            "Thebes"
        ],
        "question": "53-Who wrote the play Oedipus Rex?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b55ec9f0-e506-40b8-bc58-409022ee9c6a",
        "correctAnswer": "The part of the story from the change to the end of the story.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The part of the story from the beginning to the change in the principle character's fortunes.",
            "The resolution.",
            "The success of a story."
        ],
        "question": "54-What is the denouement?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "fca0e15d-7905-4df9-a5ca-3ff5e7b8139e",
        "correctAnswer": "The part of the story from the beginning to the change in the principle character's fortunes.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The part of the story from the change to the end of the story.",
            "The success of a story.",
            "A condition aggravating an already existing one."
        ],
        "question": "55-What is the complication?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d432d07e-1cfb-4564-9bfe-18042cefbdd0",
        "correctAnswer": "A mutton, lettuce, and tomato sandwich.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Loose change in the pocket of a person who is all dead.",
            "True love.",
            "A paper cut with lemon juice poured on it."
        ],
        "question": "56-According to Miracle Max, what is the greatest thing in the world?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e4ef901e-1610-405d-af1e-114bd116d14a",
        "correctAnswer": "Comedy of character.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Cartoons of political figures.",
            "A caricature.",
            "Physical comedy such as slapstick."
        ],
        "question": "57-What is high comedy?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7e350047-e474-4109-bdb2-ea2f904bfc4b",
        "correctAnswer": "All of these.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Cause us to pity the protagonist.",
            "To imitate action.",
            "To induce the emotions fear and pity."
        ],
        "question": "58-According to Aristotle what is tragedy's proper pleasure?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8d318041-5f14-4c98-a48a-70c56626905a",
        "correctAnswer": "Kills a man who demands that he get off the road.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Falls in love with a siren",
            "Rescues the city from a monster.",
            "Kills the king's assassin."
        ],
        "question": "59-What does Oedipus Rex do while traveling toward the city of Thebes?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b7702699-26f0-4d55-a185-ebac9c2f03ee",
        "correctAnswer": "The King and Queen of Corinth",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A Sphinx",
            "A shepherd",
            "The oracle or prophet of the god Apollo."
        ],
        "question": "60-Who raised Oedipus to be a young man?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "eadaffe9-68a5-4dea-859f-63ba3ac9b72c",
        "correctAnswer": "The characters being presented with choices.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Flashback and reminiscences",
            "Episodic plots.",
            "Dramatic structure"
        ],
        "question": "61-What causes conflict in a story?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "fe92a1ab-7dd6-4408-9507-f134086134a1",
        "correctAnswer": "His real father",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "His brother",
            "The shepherd who saved him",
            "A sphinx."
        ],
        "question": "62-Who did Oedipus fight and kill on the road to Thebes?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "95f82216-8c11-4c6e-8436-011a4a930a57",
        "correctAnswer": "The events that led up to the beginning of the play.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A story without conflict.",
            "Events portrayed in the order in which they occur.",
            "A story told in a straightforward, linear fashion."
        ],
        "question": "63-What is backstory?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2deddc73-3e73-44c8-9fc0-38e35f26d62e",
        "correctAnswer": "The main character in a story.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The main character's opponent.",
            "An extraordinary character.",
            "A representative character."
        ],
        "question": "64-What is the protagonist?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "38735b9f-64a6-42d1-be89-72b6bf3a06cc",
        "correctAnswer": "King and Queen of Thebes",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "King and Queen of Corinth",
            "A sphinx",
            "The God Apollo"
        ],
        "question": "65-The tragic tale of Oedipus Rex begins when who received a prophecy?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "46307347-a5b9-4775-876a-0e7bb952783e",
        "correctAnswer": "He rescued the city from a monster called the Sphinx.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "He exacts revenge on his mother.",
            "He fulfilled the prophecy.",
            "He killed the King's assassin."
        ],
        "question": "66-Why does the grateful city of Thebes offer the throne to Oedipus?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "13923fa3-d104-42e8-9524-bee03fe27a94",
        "correctAnswer": "Foreshadowing.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Complication",
            "Irony",
            "Peripety."
        ],
        "question": "67-In the tragedy Oedipus Rex, Oedipus questions a blind man who refuses to tell him anything. Oedipus curses him for being so uncooperative; the blind man's reply is an example of what?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "1739e24e-4c3e-4609-8593-abd152a6087d",
        "correctAnswer": "Sophocles",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Aristotle",
            "Arles",
            "Thebes"
        ],
        "question": "68-Who wrote the play Oedipus Rex?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "4e8b78b2-a93b-462d-817d-4dc023127e2e",
        "correctAnswer": "The part of the story from the change to the end of the story.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The part of the story from the beginning to the change in the principle character's fortunes.",
            "The resolution.",
            "The success of a story."
        ],
        "question": "69-What is the denouement?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d9560620-345f-4baa-b9ec-20f653741aa3",
        "correctAnswer": "The part of the story from the beginning to the change in the principle character's fortunes.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The part of the story from the change to the end of the story.",
            "The success of a story.",
            "A condition aggravating an already existing one."
        ],
        "question": "70-What is the complication?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "bd359944-d50b-465c-a89d-b06f2b2b439d",
        "correctAnswer": "A mutton, lettuce, and tomato sandwich.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Loose change in the pocket of a person who is all dead.",
            "True love.",
            "A paper cut with lemon juice poured on it."
        ],
        "question": "71-According to Miracle Max, what is the greatest thing in the world?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "6bcb8a6d-b2ee-405d-8d61-dc02cd8e1cfc",
        "correctAnswer": "Repeating the same consonant sound at the beginning of several words.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The repetition of a vowel sound anywhere in the word.",
            "The repetition of a consonant sound anywhere in the word.",
            "Words that look like they should rhyme but don't (through, rough)."
        ],
        "question": "72-What is alliteration?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d0ee7d91-22e0-4dac-a77c-39bee561c760",
        "correctAnswer": "A short poem that represents the thoughts and feelings of a given author on some topic.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A speech of a narrator or character from a drama.",
            "A story.",
            "A sweeping and long poem with a scope that is far broader than any other genre of poetry."
        ],
        "question": "73-What is a lyric poem?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3d072961-70af-4c86-9bef-b6ef8b116c31",
        "correctAnswer": "A word's dictionary definition.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Connecting and comparing two things with a form of the verb \"to be.\"",
            "A word's implication and undertone.",
            "Language that goes beyond literal meaning and exploits its words' connotation."
        ],
        "question": "74-What is denotation?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e628641d-cbf8-4581-b366-91d6b8cbff35",
        "correctAnswer": "14 lines of iambic pentameter.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Poetry that conforms to no restrictions.",
            "Perspective, all stories told from a point of view of some kind of narrator.",
            "Free verse without rhyme, rhythm and meter."
        ],
        "question": "75-What is the common form of all sonnets?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ae261575-3d19-422b-a23f-9fe40811020b",
        "correctAnswer": "A foot",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Alliteration",
            "Assonance",
            "Consonance"
        ],
        "question": "76-What do you call one repetition of a metrical pattern?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7a5ca47f-c3bd-41e4-b642-058f5592cf0a",
        "correctAnswer": "A word's dictionary definition.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Language that goes beyond literal meaning and exploits its words' connotation.",
            "A word's implication and undertone.",
            "Connecting and comparing two things with a form of the verb \"to be.\""
        ],
        "question": "77-What is denotation?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ede96092-2ead-46f4-b4de-d903d2fd355e",
        "correctAnswer": "Language that goes beyond literal meaning and exploits its words' connotation.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Connecting and comparing two things with a form of the verb \"to be.\"",
            "A word's implication and undertone",
            "A word's dictionary definition."
        ],
        "question": "78-What is figurative language?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "f4236715-e1c9-4f09-83bc-06b57ed2558f",
        "correctAnswer": "A foot",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Alliteration",
            "Assonance",
            "Consonance"
        ],
        "question": "79-What do you call one repetition of a metrical pattern?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "bfc67807-f9a3-40b5-a30d-3965187eea12",
        "correctAnswer": "False",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "True",
            ".",
            ","
        ],
        "question": "80-A dramatic poem is always an excerpt from a play.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "9f708322-0c56-4a7b-ba93-341cb8224e52",
        "correctAnswer": "Foundations myths of a given society.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "To describe the effects of evil.",
            "To reveal the narrator's character.",
            "To quickly convey the author's thoughts and emotions."
        ],
        "question": "81-What are epic poems usually used for?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8bc0fb50-ad25-4c6d-8f4a-5e4ce9963744",
        "correctAnswer": "The repetition of a consonant sound anywhere in the word.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Words that look like they should rhyme but don't (through, rough).",
            "Repeating the same consonant sound at the beginning of several words.",
            "The repetition of a vowel sound anywhere in the word."
        ],
        "question": "82-What is consonance?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d693eb39-c23c-4df6-823e-7c441f1fb51d",
        "correctAnswer": "The themes, arguments, and overall meaning of the action.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Both the way the actors enunciate the text and the literary style of the text itself.",
            "The rating.",
            "The viewer's opinion about the play or film."
        ],
        "question": "83-What is the thought of a play or film?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e3d3f977-950c-428f-9688-2c18e17fed78",
        "correctAnswer": "Sight rhyme",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Slant rhyme",
            "End rhyme",
            "Near rhyme"
        ],
        "question": "84-What do we call it when words look like they should rhyme but don't (through, rough)?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "be11de4b-2b2a-4f54-9678-22be3df294f3",
        "correctAnswer": "A foot",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Assonance",
            "Alliteration",
            "Consonance"
        ],
        "question": "85-What do you call one repetition of a metrical pattern?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b3549825-d585-4282-8704-07419a17753a",
        "correctAnswer": "Five",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Four",
            "Six",
            "Eight"
        ],
        "question": "86-How many feet does iambic pentameter have?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0f6d7aba-5db9-420d-8bb4-d72c2397a3d0",
        "correctAnswer": "The Protestant Reformation",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Building of monasteries",
            "The Crusades",
            "The birth of modern nation states"
        ],
        "question": "87-What was not an important event of the Middle Ages?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e2602f55-66e7-44be-9525-61ee1d007814",
        "correctAnswer": "An improvement in agriculture and the birth of early European nation states.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The conversion of the Vikings.",
            "The philosophies of Aristotle.",
            "The invention of the printing press."
        ],
        "question": "88-What brought back a modicum of prosperity and security in the second half of the Middle Ages?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "300841c9-5415-4aec-adf6-616a229d5213",
        "correctAnswer": "The idea is perfect and unchanging.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The idea is unformed and therefore malleable.",
            "Ideas are free.",
            "Ideas are easier to create than actual objects."
        ],
        "question": "89-Why did Plato consider the idea of a chair more important than an actual chair?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ace671ec-e212-485d-9995-439d5a1bd282",
        "correctAnswer": "Reims Cathedral",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Paris",
            "Castillon",
            "Clovis"
        ],
        "question": "90-Where were the French Kings crowned?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "554ab4ea-d5e7-4954-a820-e3534807a99d",
        "correctAnswer": "Style",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Composition",
            "Tone",
            "Genre"
        ],
        "question": "91-What is the result of the many choices an artist makes regarding the medium, elements, and form of their art?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e4eac54a-9fb9-423b-9d1f-6ab379dca2ed",
        "correctAnswer": "Ascent of the soul into the intellectual world",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Death",
            "Man's Search for Happiness",
            "Resurrection"
        ],
        "question": "92-In the famous \"Allegory of the Cave,\" our text explains that leaving the cave or the upward journey represents:",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "1f601040-acff-451b-9473-40cce74426ba",
        "correctAnswer": "The Protestant Reformation",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Building of monasteries",
            "The Crusades",
            "The birth of modern nation states"
        ],
        "question": "93-What was not an important event of the Middle Ages?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2224df54-eba6-47cd-ab9c-b8d1136b9e2b",
        "correctAnswer": "He loved tragedy.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "He favored censorship of music.",
            "He believed young people should avoid slothful or lustful music.",
            "He believed the universe was created according to musical principles."
        ],
        "question": "94-What is not true about Plato?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "86081cd0-1e07-4476-bba1-2926ead95d46",
        "correctAnswer": "The world of sight",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The birth of the world",
            "Industrial future",
            "Agriculture past"
        ],
        "question": "95-In the famous \"Allegory of the Cave,\" what does the cave, or prison-house, represent?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "fe5055fa-0178-4a2f-9756-7f1d2d661481",
        "correctAnswer": "Exemplary, of top quality, outstanding",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Out-dated or old",
            "Revival",
            "Dionysian"
        ],
        "question": "96-What does the word classic mean?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0e2c2509-00bf-4e1b-a29a-534585678d68",
        "correctAnswer": "Rebirth",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "End of ancient times",
            "Human freedom",
            "Protestant Reformation"
        ],
        "question": "97-What does the name renaissance mean?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c6c70311-a611-4b73-8d86-6ea22f2b9e22",
        "correctAnswer": "The idea is perfect and unchanging.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The idea is unformed and therefore malleable.",
            "Ideas are free.",
            "Ideas are easier to create than actual objects."
        ],
        "question": "98-Why did Plato consider the idea of a chair more important than an actual chair?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3edc879e-2cad-4464-af4b-87cfa8a02b11",
        "correctAnswer": "Metaphysics",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Epicureanism",
            "Stoicism",
            "Cynicism"
        ],
        "question": "99-What branch of philosophy deals with the question, \"What is real\"?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "59e1063d-d28c-4b74-aa11-08a9c1ca8098",
        "correctAnswer": "Romans were so impressed with Greek culture that they made it their own and spread it throughout the world.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Greek soldiers used a trojan horse to sneak inside the gates of Rome.",
            "German barbarians conquered the western half of the Roman empire in 500 A.D.",
            "Barbarian depredations, political disorder, and a drastic population decrease marked the beginning of the Dark Ages."
        ],
        "question": "100-The old saying \"Rome conquered Greece but Greece conquered Rome\" means:",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2e204876-c060-46ce-9bd3-9105955b7432",
        "correctAnswer": "Ancient, Middle Ages, Modern",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Old Kingdom, Middle Kingdom, New Kingdom",
            "Mesopotamian history, Dark Ages, Modern history",
            "Age of Discovery, Renaissance, Protestant Reformation"
        ],
        "question": "101-In HUM 110, we will divide the history of the world into what three parts:",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "90239f3b-bac4-4a85-b1e7-ea3ca642faec",
        "correctAnswer": "Van Eyck",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Peter Brueghel The Elder and Peter Brueghel The Younger",
            "Rembrandt",
            "Petrus Christus"
        ],
        "question": "102-Which set of brothers were pioneers in the development of oil paint?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "4e3a24be-f630-4f41-8a48-e4adfcb5acd9",
        "correctAnswer": "Hellenistic",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Late Bronze Age",
            "Byzantine",
            "Neolithic"
        ],
        "question": "103-What was the name of the Greek style as it spread throughout the Mediterranean world in the second and first centuries BCE?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ffd7cd0b-6003-41a5-a33e-8dc68b08c6ad",
        "correctAnswer": "The intersecting arch.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The spinning wheel allowed for tapestries to be mass produced.",
            "Evil spirits that might try to move into the cathedral were scared away.",
            "Astronomical clocks."
        ],
        "question": "104-What was the technological advance of the Gothic style?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a62c8034-bd45-4e3e-ba38-73a4548540f1",
        "correctAnswer": "To influence the things of the natural world, to bring about a successful hunt.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "To express deep emotions without words.",
            "Because it's fun to make things.",
            "To give comfort to those who had died."
        ],
        "question": "105-Why do we think the Lascaux cave painters created their art?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "fd22e736-2d9c-4bd7-97ce-08d36609bed0",
        "correctAnswer": "To show the objects from their best, most recognizable angle so that they have the most direct and powerful influence over the next life.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "It was the best the primitive people could do.",
            "It's a joke, similar to a caricature.",
            "To emphasize the importance of the physical body."
        ],
        "question": "106-Why do Egyptian paintings show some parts of the body straight on and some in profile?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "55e4d362-9361-47aa-a2c6-dd926aa40b30",
        "correctAnswer": "The intersecting arch.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The spinning wheel allowed for tapestries to be mass produced.",
            "Evil spirits that might try to move into the cathedral were scared away.",
            "Astronomical clocks."
        ],
        "question": "107-What was the technological advance of the Gothic style?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3532a75a-046c-4a74-b848-5ea1c636a8ce",
        "correctAnswer": "Giotto",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Rembrandt",
            "Van Eyck",
            "Michelangelo"
        ],
        "question": "108-Which artist led the realistic revolution in painting in the 1300s?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2624568b-26a9-4ce6-afce-8ee07236e02c",
        "correctAnswer": "A spiritual reality",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "An object's best, most recognizable angle",
            "Political reality",
            "Natural settings"
        ],
        "question": "109-What did the Byzantines seek to show rather than physical realism?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "fecebcc3-7df0-448b-aca9-69f10350ef65",
        "correctAnswer": "Baby Jesus as a little man",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Apostle Paul",
            "John the Baptist",
            "The Angel Gabriel"
        ],
        "question": "110-\"Madonna and Child\" illustrates that Byzantine art is uninterested in a physical realism. This painting shows who with frontal views, stern expressions, and oversized eyes:",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "6dfec1d5-9aa6-47eb-911e-7597aa95f5a7",
        "correctAnswer": "A spiritual reality",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "An object's best, most recognizable angle",
            "Political reality",
            "Natural settings"
        ],
        "question": "111-What did the Byzantines seek to show rather than physical realism?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2b7710fe-7aa9-4e13-b18f-70ec452b5003",
        "correctAnswer": "Build high walls with stained-glass windows",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Build concrete foundations",
            "Insulate walls, ceilings, and floors",
            "Use steel rods to reinforce walls and ceilings"
        ],
        "question": "112-What did the technological advances of the Gothic style allow Gothic builders to do?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5db7c16b-7f36-4c8e-b0f5-3bb8c11c237e",
        "correctAnswer": "The portrait bust",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Relief",
            "Monumental sculpture",
            "Free-standing sculptures"
        ],
        "question": "113-What form of sculpture is uniquely Roman?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8fd5099c-18a9-4cad-a74b-80548be57bbb",
        "correctAnswer": "Expression",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Form",
            "Neither",
            "Both"
        ],
        "question": "114-Does Hellenistic art favor form or expression?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a8ec2025-5fae-48ef-988f-c779f0384def",
        "correctAnswer": "Hellenistic",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Late Bronze Age",
            "Byzantine",
            "Neolithic"
        ],
        "question": "115-What was the name of the Greek style as it spread throughout the Mediterranean world in the second and first centuries BCE?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d3cd602a-e43a-4a1e-938a-ee6f8d1d4a95",
        "correctAnswer": "France and England",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Scotland and Ireland",
            "France and Scotland",
            "England and Spain"
        ],
        "question": "116-Who were the main combatants in the Hundred Years War?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3c2f0603-f6b4-436f-a43e-076600bf0556",
        "correctAnswer": "The Fall of Rome",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The 100 Years War",
            "The Fall of Greece",
            "The Bubonic Plague"
        ],
        "question": "117-What event signaled the beginning of the Dark Ages?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "be5c7e2b-5101-4c5c-bdfd-b101c767ecbe",
        "correctAnswer": "Johannes Gutenberg",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Christopher Columbus",
            "John Wycliffe",
            "William Tyndale"
        ],
        "question": "118-Who brought moveable type to Europe?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "f0d4ef5d-fb8e-490c-a482-0d075471c302",
        "correctAnswer": "Constantine",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Augustus",
            "Claudius",
            "Maximinus"
        ],
        "question": "119-Which Roman emperor made Byzantium his capital?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a7f78635-70bb-492a-9073-a7421437c152",
        "correctAnswer": "The understanding that the earth was round",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Fall of Constantinople",
            "The end of the Hundred Years War",
            "The invention of movable type"
        ],
        "question": "120-Which event did NOT occurr in 1453, signaling the end of the Middle Ages?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7ee6503d-b714-4dbf-8a34-1849395bbfc0",
        "correctAnswer": "Farms",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Small towns",
            "Palaces",
            "Cities"
        ],
        "question": "121-Where did most people live in 1453?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5a21942b-fb5e-4ddf-a5c1-0fd86f5d2376",
        "correctAnswer": "France and England",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "England and Spain",
            "Scotland and Ireland",
            "France and Scotland"
        ],
        "question": "122-Who were the main combatants in the Hundred Years War?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "9d11939e-3eba-4532-bc52-743183a6e99f",
        "correctAnswer": "Lice/Fleas",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Germs",
            "Gnats",
            "Atoms"
        ],
        "question": "123-What were the smallest living things anyone knew about in 1453? Select all that apply.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7e07dbc5-dc25-4cad-a4d5-df801030ab38",
        "correctAnswer": "The Fall of Rome",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The 100 Years War",
            "The Bubonic Plague",
            "The Fall of Greece"
        ],
        "question": "124-What event signaled the beginning of the Dark Ages?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "51af61ad-d02a-49b7-8475-4c5ec037e8de",
        "correctAnswer": "Joan of Arc",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Saint Anthony",
            "King John II",
            "King Henry V"
        ],
        "question": "125-Which leader inspired victory in the Hundred Year War?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3ed81957-9e41-4d7a-9d7b-11915290b52a",
        "correctAnswer": "Johannes Gutenberg",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "William Tyndale",
            "Christopher Columbus",
            "John Wycliffe"
        ],
        "question": "126-Who brought moveable type to Europe?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ccb88fbb-9f67-4566-9e1f-04f38603fce1",
        "correctAnswer": "The Battle at Crecy",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Fall of Rome",
            "The Fall of Constantinople",
            "The Battle of Calias"
        ],
        "question": "127-What battle marked the end of medieval warfare?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "4c1fe38d-7c10-4041-a9b9-9bab539b371d",
        "correctAnswer": "Farms",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Small towns",
            "Cities",
            "Palaces"
        ],
        "question": "128-Where did most people live in 1453?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "28047d8f-3f5e-4891-bf99-0d5f0a51d348",
        "correctAnswer": "Joan of Arc",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "King John II",
            "Saint Anthony",
            "King Henry V"
        ],
        "question": "129-Which leader inspired victory in the Hundred Year War?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "20c00a00-4216-48a4-9960-4538c4011f86",
        "correctAnswer": "The Bubonic Plague, or the Black Death",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The 100 Years War",
            "The Fall of Rome",
            "Poor hygiene"
        ],
        "question": "130-What catastrophe reduced the population of Europe in the 1300's and 1400's?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e1e52ee6-55c5-4f9c-bd18-a7a05a8277f4",
        "correctAnswer": "Marco Polo",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Plato",
            "Herman Melville",
            "Geoffrey Chaucer"
        ],
        "question": "131-Who wrote a book about a Venetian party traveling to China?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0634f386-fb47-44f5-bb15-2dc783d992d9",
        "correctAnswer": "John Calvin",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Martin Luther",
            "Henry Vlll",
            "John Wycliffe"
        ],
        "question": "132-Which Protestant reformer insisted that churches be stripped of idolatrous images?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "77561b87-17c2-425d-a416-11f02cc8ba7e",
        "correctAnswer": "It made them less interested in the things of this world.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "It made them more interested in natural phenomenon.",
            "It made them more interested in the human body.",
            "It made them less interested in religion."
        ],
        "question": "133-How did Plato's ideas affect the art of the Middle Ages?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "40dcc1c3-36d4-4dcb-bb82-987ac57d87a9",
        "correctAnswer": "Galileo",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Roger Bacon",
            "Michelangelo",
            "William of Ockham"
        ],
        "question": "134-Who proved the Copernican model of the solar system using a telescope?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "29646759-0ebd-4921-86c7-a914a2b31d37",
        "correctAnswer": "The Council of Trent",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The creation of the Jesuits",
            "The Protestant Reformation",
            "The 30 Years War"
        ],
        "question": "135-What was the key event of the Counter-Reformation?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "268d67c8-9522-4a5d-b46b-ec65ef93b517",
        "correctAnswer": "John Calvin",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "John Wycliffe",
            "Henry Vlll",
            "Martin Luther"
        ],
        "question": "136-Which Protestant reformer insisted that churches be stripped of idolatrous images?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d1a4f2e5-48c0-4f98-817a-a1e7db9ad573",
        "correctAnswer": "Lorenzo de Medici",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Leonardo da Vinci",
            "Andrea del Verrocchio",
            "Sandro Botticelli"
        ],
        "question": "137-What rich political leader was an important patron of the arts in Florence?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "80a864f8-4469-4c55-81cc-8e85e463c366",
        "correctAnswer": "The civilizations of the Greeks and Romans and the Renaissance",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Greeks and the Renaissance",
            "The civilizations of the Greeks and Romans",
            "The Babylonians and the Renaissance"
        ],
        "question": "138-What was the \"Middle Ages\" the middle of?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c8cda56b-0004-446f-9c0d-102552a9a20d",
        "correctAnswer": "Marco Polo",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Plato",
            "Geoffrey Chaucer",
            "Herman Melville"
        ],
        "question": "139-Who wrote a book about a Venetian party traveling to China?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d24bc28d-e47a-4275-95e0-62aa99db2af9",
        "correctAnswer": "Galileo",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Michelangelo",
            "William of Ockham",
            "Roger Bacon"
        ],
        "question": "140-Who proved the Copernican model of the solar system using a telescope?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7af6bb41-f13f-4e44-b292-dde8c37ce10b",
        "correctAnswer": "Galileo",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Michelangelo",
            "Roger Bacon",
            "William of Ockham"
        ],
        "question": "141-Who proved the Copernican model of the solar system using a telescope?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "23e6cc8c-cd47-4eab-aef4-62b0650863fb",
        "correctAnswer": "So he could divorce his first wife.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "So he could ignore the Pope.",
            "So he could support John Calvin.",
            "So he could be the Pope."
        ],
        "question": "142-Why did Henry VIII lead England out of the Roman Catholic Church?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "05a5fb71-d2eb-48b5-bed7-d7708716bde2",
        "correctAnswer": "The burial place of Peter the Apostle",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The site of the Pentecost",
            "A battle ground won by the Warrior Pope, Julius the 2nd",
            "The hill where Peter preached to the Romans"
        ],
        "question": "143-St. Peter's Basilica was originally built over what place?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2c9c5461-2cf1-40d9-b465-a47f7312c4ea",
        "correctAnswer": "Reconquista",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "La Resistencia",
            "Guerra de Libertad",
            "Conquista"
        ],
        "question": "144-What did the Spanish call their war to take back Spain from the Muslims?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a060f36f-1515-47ed-ba08-914b428da01d",
        "correctAnswer": "Empiricism",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "historicism",
            "idealism",
            "rationalism"
        ],
        "question": "145-What is the word for the belief that mankind's only access to truth is through the senses?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5beb280e-65d3-4564-8529-e2ea13bfdfc1",
        "correctAnswer": "A dagger",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The King",
            "A sword",
            "His wife"
        ],
        "question": "146-Before the murder, Macbeth sees a vision. What is it of?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7974fbc0-704e-4e5b-a98e-e9c626a562d8",
        "correctAnswer": "Because his conscience will keep him from sleeping again",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Because he is an insomniac",
            "Because Duncan is the King of Sleep",
            "Because Macbeth will not sleep that night"
        ],
        "question": "147-Why does Macbeth say \"Macbeth does murder sleep\"?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3b88556f-2a89-462f-85d4-fcf458a374c6",
        "correctAnswer": "Their beards",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Macbeth's doubt",
            "Their faces",
            "Their hands"
        ],
        "question": "148-What makes Banquo doubt that the witches are women?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8068c0d0-0fbe-4d40-b19e-a94e9a31b9b7",
        "correctAnswer": "Unrhymed iambic pentameter",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Rhymed iambic pentameter",
            "Unrhymed monometer",
            "Rhymed monometer"
        ],
        "question": "149-What is blank verse?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b7257248-750d-4bd2-a64b-0b29c7a706bf",
        "correctAnswer": "He made Banquo, James' ancestor, innocent of the murder.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "He made Macbeth doubt.",
            "He made Malcom, James' ancestor, innocent of the murder.",
            "He insulted Banquo by saying he is not a man."
        ],
        "question": "150-How did Shakespeare adapt the story of Macbeth to suit the tastes of James I, King of England?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a661488c-0806-4328-a382-734c23022daf",
        "correctAnswer": "When a single character speaks their thoughts aloud not intending other characters to hear",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "When the audience knows something the character does not",
            "When a character speaks their thoughts aloud to another character",
            "When a character speaks directly to the audience"
        ],
        "question": "152-What is a soliloquy?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d63a4272-4d3e-4fc4-92f1-907a1d29b002",
        "correctAnswer": "The original thane was executed for treason",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The original thane fled to England",
            "The original thane died in the war",
            "The original thane was his father"
        ],
        "question": "153-How did Macbeth get to be Thane of Cawdor?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "357342a7-1116-46af-8d43-f839044023d9",
        "correctAnswer": "The Thane of Cawdor",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The King of England",
            "The King of Scotland",
            "The Thane of Glenco"
        ],
        "question": "154-Of whom does Malcolm say, \"Nothing in his life Became him like the leaving it\"?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a4271015-9fac-481a-801f-f189c97a3a64",
        "correctAnswer": "Duncan",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Banquo",
            "Malcolm",
            "Macbeth"
        ],
        "question": "155-Who is the king of Scotland at the beginning of the play?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "38a040b5-4afe-435d-8667-85245d3c0a2c",
        "correctAnswer": "Calling him a coward and not a man",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Calls him a coward and a drunk",
            "Insulting his manhood by saying he had no courage",
            "Insulting him by saying he is not a man"
        ],
        "question": "157-When Macbeth hesitates, how does Lady Macbeth persuade him to go through with the awful deed?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2a4a189f-8962-4919-a19d-f17b25f01c1e",
        "correctAnswer": "The original thane was executed for treason",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The original thane fled to England",
            "The original thane died in the war",
            "The original thane was his father"
        ],
        "question": "158-How did Macbeth get to be Thane of Cawdor?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5071d7ba-972b-495c-9f1f-04553da46a59",
        "correctAnswer": "The Thane of Cawdor",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Thane of Glenco",
            "The King of England",
            "The King of Scotland"
        ],
        "question": "159-Of whom does Malcolm say, \"Nothing in his life Became him like the leaving it\"?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "33594236-184d-4681-bb3e-a57ea92950fc",
        "correctAnswer": "She keeps trying to wash the blood off her hands",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "She has visions of blood on the ground",
            "She keeps trying to wash a freckle off her hand",
            "She has visions of the murdered king"
        ],
        "question": "160-What is the nature of Lady Macbeth's madness?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "123443af-e0c3-4037-8d72-05f4791f42c4",
        "correctAnswer": "The invading soldiers camouflaged themselves with tree branches",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The invading soldiers brought battering rams made in Birnam Wood",
            "The invading soldiers lived in Birnam Wood",
            "The invading soldiers brought ladders made in Birnam Wood"
        ],
        "question": "161-How did Birnam Wood come to Dunsinane?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "701df063-5535-4d87-ba57-9aa5f21bb614",
        "correctAnswer": "Scorpions",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Hornets",
            "Witches' lies",
            "Darkness"
        ],
        "question": "162-What does Macbeth say his mind is full of?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a32e78eb-9062-455a-8ba7-f1a10e3c0f13",
        "correctAnswer": "He escapes",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "He is murdered",
            "He drowns",
            "He is put in prison"
        ],
        "question": "163-What happens to Fleance?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "95335dca-a18c-4e95-8171-291efff5bec6",
        "correctAnswer": "The three witches",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Lady Macduff",
            "Lady Macbeth",
            "Hectate"
        ],
        "question": "164-Who says \"Double, Double, Toil and Trouble\"?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "98625a65-dc00-479c-8e23-66601e14fba8",
        "correctAnswer": "She keeps trying to wash the blood off her hands",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "She has visions of the murdered king",
            "She keeps trying to wash a freckle off her hand",
            "She has visions of blood on the ground"
        ],
        "question": "165-What is the nature of Lady Macbeth's madness?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2b6700d7-e66a-4f91-a0b7-139d3646a7a7",
        "correctAnswer": "Malcolm",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Fleance",
            "Duncan",
            "Banquo"
        ],
        "question": "166-Who is king at the end of the play?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c133796c-877e-453e-8014-db8e41639673",
        "correctAnswer": "An armed head, a bloody child, and a royal child",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "An armed head, a royal child, and a tree branch",
            "A bloody child, a royal child, and wolf",
            "An armed head, a bloody child and a dagger"
        ],
        "question": "167-What three apparitions do the witches call up for Macbeth?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a0f6795d-0b54-4b80-be46-b11660da9299",
        "correctAnswer": "To be born by Caesarian Section",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "To be born of Hectate, Mother of Magic",
            "To be born of the Fae, Spirits of the land",
            "To be born of the earth as was Adam"
        ],
        "question": "168-How is it possible to not be \"of a woman born\"?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "badbb64b-9dba-4610-b8b1-d2cbf5ecdce1",
        "correctAnswer": "The witches say he would be the ancestor of kings",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The witches say that he will kill Macbeth",
            "The witches say he was greater than Macbeth",
            "The witches say he would be king"
        ],
        "question": "169-Why does Macbeth fear Banquo?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a7b0e4ce-bee5-4647-b0f4-745343c12ef9",
        "correctAnswer": "timpani or kettledrum, cymbals, xylophone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "lute, recorder, sitar",
            "bassoon, piccolo, tuba",
            "french horn, harp, trombone"
        ],
        "question": "170-Indicate three percussion instruments:",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "27ee39c6-ebd8-4898-bad7-5c617bb6c016",
        "correctAnswer": "Roman arches, Barrel vaults, Small windows, Stacked levels",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Intersecting arches and High ceilings",
            "Giant stained glass windows",
            "Flying buttresses and cement used for building"
        ],
        "question": "171-What characterizes Romanesque architecture?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "41ce0597-51d0-4162-a4e7-87ff3bbc1ee5",
        "correctAnswer": "Hellenistic",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Gothic",
            "Romanesque",
            "Corinthian"
        ],
        "question": "172-What was the name of the Greek style as it spread throughout the Mediterranean world in the second and first centuries BCE?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "74cae008-829f-4932-8221-3634468934ee",
        "correctAnswer": " expression",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "form",
            "medium",
            "themes"
        ],
        "question": "173-6.\tWhich does Hellenistic art favor?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "78c58214-c377-4e63-adc9-c97444742ad2",
        "correctAnswer": "? spiritual or symbolic reality",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "physical realism",
            "emotional expression",
            "innovation"
        ],
        "question": "174-What did the Byzantines seek to show?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "72438b28-a84b-4c8d-beca-4dfa6cf9f81d",
        "correctAnswer": "Portrait bust",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "marble sculpture",
            "oil painting",
            "fresco painting"
        ],
        "question": "175-What form of sculpture is uniquely Roman?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5e297a3b-2001-486c-b781-39e0276e1577",
        "correctAnswer": "The human body",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Spirituality",
            "prophecy",
            "landscapes"
        ],
        "question": "176-What artistic subject did the Greeks love most?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5b9cc1f0-d019-423e-81ed-483abd5ff565",
        "correctAnswer": "to show in two dimensions the best views of a three-dimensional figure.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "to confuse people",
            "to please the gods",
            "to scare people"
        ],
        "question": "177-Why do Egyptian paintings show some parts of the body straight on and some in profile?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "251903af-1d86-4d96-903d-68f50e94e2a2",
        "correctAnswer": "to bring comforts to their dead",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "to show off",
            "to please the gods",
            "to cause emotions"
        ],
        "question": "178-Why did the ancient Egyptians create their art?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "cfcd52c6-16c4-4156-897f-cb43e9a4f5a2",
        "correctAnswer": "probably intended to influence an upcoming hunt by depicting images of great bounty",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "to record events for the future generations",
            "to make their surroundings less drab",
            "to laud their accomplishments"
        ],
        "question": "179-Why do we think the Lascaux cave painters created their art?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "280660c4-60aa-4b21-8999-be05f8125fe7",
        "correctAnswer": "metaphysics",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Empiricism",
            "mathematics",
            "science"
        ],
        "question": "180-What branch of philosophy deals with the question, \"What is real\"?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "4ccdb426-6771-4fdc-b11a-3e3c4f62a2f3",
        "correctAnswer": "empiricism",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "metaphysics",
            "mathematics",
            "science"
        ],
        "question": "181-6.\tWhat do we call the belief that our five senses are our only access to truth?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3f9e0a2f-3712-464f-a9ff-433a8c8696d8",
        "correctAnswer": "math",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "science",
            "philosophy",
            "Magic"
        ],
        "question": "182-To Plato and Pythagoras, what other study was most closely related to Music?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c4936285-4a58-41ff-aa63-06ba8ba54628",
        "correctAnswer": "Socrates",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Aristotle",
            "Leonardo da Vinci",
            "Lorenzo de Medici"
        ],
        "question": "183-Who was Plato's teacher?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "9dc10369-0473-4600-aa14-899b6625d956",
        "correctAnswer": "Aristotle",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Socrates",
            "Caesar Augustus",
            "Mark Anthony"
        ],
        "question": "184-Who was Plato's student?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "9b20b7a2-9270-4c58-b3ce-110d34f4c638",
        "correctAnswer": "Pythagoras",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Socrates",
            "Aristotle",
            "Michelangelo"
        ],
        "question": "185-4.\tWhat philosopher influenced Plato with his teachings that the universe was created according to musical and mathematical proportions?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d5fd40cf-078d-43cb-9d16-40d2121910af",
        "correctAnswer": "Constantine",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "188-Who was the first Roman emperor to embrace Christianity?",
            "189-What event is used to mark the end of Ancient times?"
        ],
        "question": "187-Who led the French to victory in the Hundred Years War?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "08e39147-f18d-486a-8136-fc9ee1b49e31",
        "correctAnswer": "Rebirth",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "190-6.\tWhat is the first half of the Middle Ages called?",
            "191-7.\tWhat does the name renaissance mean?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! the western half of the Roman Empire fell to German barbarians",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "1d2246c3-8ed5-456f-bcfd-552ee273f605",
        "correctAnswer": "Banquo\u2019s son",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "193-Who is Fleance?",
            "Duncan's son"
        ],
        "question": "192-8.\tWhat does the word classic mean?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c8371adb-e32a-4f69-9d4f-16c520350347",
        "correctAnswer": "  Banquo",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Ross' son",
            "194-\u2022\tWho appears to Macbeth at the banquet?",
            "195-\u2022\tWhat do Malcolm and Donalbain do after Duncan's murder?"
        ],
        "question": "Macduff's son",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "eb573379-db51-408c-bab7-fe052414fccf",
        "correctAnswer": "  Entropy",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "196-\u2022\tHow does Lady Macbeth get blood on her hands?",
            "197-1.\tWhat is the name of the scientific principle where matter proceeds from order to disorder?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct!   They escaped, one to Ireland, one to England.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "09043eb1-f5ba-4ee3-a6cf-c4d8dd4cd648",
        "correctAnswer": "  Dionysius",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "199-1.\tWho was the Greek god of wine?",
            "200-2.\tWhat instrument did worshippers of Apollo play?"
        ],
        "question": "198-2.\tWhat did Blaise Pascal say that we should always do in difficult times?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b2b6775c-ac96-4370-8cb8-49a9d6330c82",
        "correctAnswer": "   Painting, sculpture, architecture can be considered space art.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "201-4.\tWhich art form is not a \"time art\"?",
            "202-5.\tArt forms that are time art: music or literature",
            "203-6.\tWhat is music with a subject called?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct!   Lyre",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "4169f919-c809-48b3-85bb-670ec83e1c8b",
        "correctAnswer": " absolute music.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "program music.",
            "204-What is Music without a subject called?",
            "205-2.\tWhat do we call the beam across the top of two posts?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct!   Music with a subject is known as",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "bf78c712-6a6c-4d3b-a3f7-302994a607bf",
        "correctAnswer": "Arches create an oculus or ring open to the sky",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "206-3.\tWhat was the new building material the Romans used?",
            "207-6.\tWhat is unique about the dome of the Pantheon?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! You have two posts on the left and right of your door, and a lintel, or a board across the top held up by the two posts.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ea6b4dd8-0e47-4d85-8a7d-9ba4a3cb7f90",
        "correctAnswer": "A cappella.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "209-2.\tWhat is singing without any accompaniment called?",
            "210-1.\tWhat do we call instruments with reeds?"
        ],
        "question": "208-What was the greatest influence on architecture between the fall of Rome and the 1100s?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d4f112a2-a3bf-4b1b-ba56-8879d16a4752",
        "correctAnswer": "Piano hammer that strike strings, harpsichord\u2019s quills pluck strings",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "211-2.\tName the members of the brass family?",
            "212-8.\tWhat is the difference between a harpsichord and a piano?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Woodwinds.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ba9229d1-5dfb-4722-92ca-72fa279145b4",
        "correctAnswer": "Meter.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "214-2.\tWhat do we call a grouping of beats that creates pattern?",
            "215-3.\tWhat do we call a tone with a regularly repeating pattern or rate of vibration?"
        ],
        "question": "213-1.\tWhat is an example of free rhythm?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ec4b1c45-412f-4f2a-936f-e5cfad26626c",
        "correctAnswer": "Triple meter.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "216-4.\tIn a 2/4 time signature, how many beats are in each measure?",
            "217-5.\tWhat meter is a waltz in?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Pitch.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "030b2f60-c14a-421f-aee5-1c37b91ddeca",
        "correctAnswer": "Timbre",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "219-7.\tWhat is the musical term for tone color?",
            "220-8.\tWhat is the difference between a major and a minor scale?"
        ],
        "question": "218-6.\tWhat meter is a march in?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0321e3de-27ff-498f-a604-3d429f5368bb",
        "correctAnswer": "Conjunct.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "221-9.\tWhat is the term for the distance between two pitches?",
            "222-10.\tWhat do we call a melody that is mostly made-up steps?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Where the half steps fall.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "f7a16f21-df90-4443-8c6e-0580c1e1556a",
        "correctAnswer": "monophony, 1 Melody. Homophony, Melody and harmony. Polyphony, more than two melodies simultaneously",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "224-13.\tWhat is the difference between monophony, homophony, and polyphony?",
            "225-Put the following in order from slowest to fastest: largo, presto, andante, allegro, moderato."
        ],
        "question": "223-12.\tWhat is the term for a group of notes sounded simultaneously?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "89043ab2-329d-4c6c-b3ec-e60e50d09f97",
        "correctAnswer": "I. M. PEI.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "226-Put the following in order from softest to loudest: fortissimo, mezzo piano, piano, forte, mezzo forte.",
            "227-1.\tWhich architect designed the Louvre pyramid?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Largo, Adante, moderato, allegro, Vivace, Presto",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8e42c5aa-5ee5-436d-a839-18fd0d47fe20",
        "correctAnswer": "SFUMATO or smokiness.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "229-3.\tWhat technique does Leonardo use to make the smile of the Mona Lisa so mysterious?",
            "230-1.\tWhat is the term for a liquid that combines with a pigment to make paint?"
        ],
        "question": "228-2.\tWhat was the Louvre before it was a museum?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8502acb9-8994-4679-a221-3c467abbb73f",
        "correctAnswer": "Mixing pigments with water, runs easily, need heavy, damp paper so colors will stick better",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "231-2.\tWhat are the characteristics of oil paint?",
            "232-3.\tWhat are the characteristics of watercolor paint?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Vehicle.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e35e0483-d92d-45a5-b0ae-9f4eaa544730",
        "correctAnswer": "Painted on dry plaster can crack or flake and/or fade",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "234-5.\tWhat are the characteristics of a mural?",
            "235-6.\tWhat artistic medium is made with egg?"
        ],
        "question": "233-4.\tWhat are the characteristics of a fresco?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "44e9fd81-05b9-47de-9079-04ff5198a2d0",
        "correctAnswer": "Etching.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "236-7.\tWhich artistic medium did Michelangelo use to paint the Sistine Chapel?",
            "237-8.\tWhich artistic medium uses acid on a plate?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Tempura.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "62f5d3c2-0dbb-4984-b731-48ed5deb9760",
        "correctAnswer": "Low.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "239-10.\tWhat does Bas in bas relief mean?",
            "240-1.\tWhat does a horizontal line indicate?"
        ],
        "question": "238-9.\tIn what medium does an artist arrange pieces of glass, tile, stone, or other objects to make a picture?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "f19d3579-dd35-4b33-bfe3-afa4d19a7b37",
        "correctAnswer": "Potential energy.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "241-2.\tWhat does a diagonal line indicate?",
            "242-3.\tWhat does a vertical line indicate?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Rest or stability.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c714614d-406d-4697-8121-3a237cdb8b7f",
        "correctAnswer": "Red.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "244-7.\tWhich is warmest color?",
            "245-What does the element value refer to in a painting?"
        ],
        "question": "243-6.\tWhich is the coolest color?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d2ff6774-0658-4765-80ab-958b02f51ee3",
        "correctAnswer": "Shows distance to the use of lines.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "246-What does chiaroscuro refer to?",
            "247-What is linear perspective?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Relative degree of light or darkness",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "044e4ff3-d745-40e2-9945-e80217e0ce02",
        "correctAnswer": "Divide scene into thirds, draw horizontal and vertical lines, and then place the most important part of the scene near one of the intersecting points",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "249-1.\tWhere should you generally put the subject of your photo?",
            "250-2.\tWhere is the ISO automatically set in most cameras?"
        ],
        "question": "248-What is aerial perspective?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "93048897-fdc6-4e34-aab4-87f95c63409a",
        "correctAnswer": "To compensate for the backlighting of the sun and overcome hard shadows.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "251-3.\tHow can you avoid red-eye?",
            "252-4.\tWhy would you want to use a flash outdoors?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! 800.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "f6e766bf-81a7-4879-bdbc-ec7ed847603f",
        "correctAnswer": " Pride",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "254-1.\tWhat is hubris?",
            "255-2.\tWhat did the oracle of Delphi prophesy about Oedipus?"
        ],
        "question": "253-5.\tWhat is \"bull's-eye\" composition?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "96d0ab46-b4f0-43bb-8c2a-2ea506f1e35d",
        "correctAnswer": " all from the beginning of the story to the point just before the change in the hero's fortunes",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "256-1.\tWhat are Aristotle's six elements of tragedy?",
            "257-2.\tWhat is the complication?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct!   That he would kill his father and marry his mother.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b49511b4-3e1c-4717-88df-e5993b345784",
        "correctAnswer": " to increase our fear on behalf of our hero.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "259-4.\tAccording to Aristotle, what is the purpose of the complication in a tragedy?",
            "260-5.\tAccording to Aristotle, what is the purpose of a denouement in a tragedy?"
        ],
        "question": "258-3.\tWhat is the denouement?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d40b030f-17e5-45f3-b402-49c981c532ae",
        "correctAnswer": " a Greek word that means \"purification\"",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "6.\tWhat word does Aristotle use to describe a shift from one situation to its opposite?",
            "7.\tWhat does catharsis mean?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct!  the opportunity for the audience to feel pity for the hero",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0140f297-9e86-482c-ab52-c75b34320fe2",
        "correctAnswer": " comedy of character, and it seeks to give as accurate a portrayal of people as possible, and in watching it we usually smile a lot, and sometimes cry, because these people remind us of ourselves or people we have known.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "9.\tWhat is high comedy?",
            "10.\tWhat is low comedy?"
        ],
        "question": "8.\tIn a tragic catharsis, what happens to the audience's emotions?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    }
]